<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyTithe</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="enter_tithe">Enter Your Income</string>
    <string name="findmytith">Find MyTithe</string>
    <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-8831705983843599~1119760461</string>
    <string name="ad_unit">ca-app-pub-8831705983843599/3834210258</string>
    <string name="ad_test">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="welcome_myTithe">Welcome To MyTithe</string>
    <string name="enter_amount">Enter Amount </string>
    <string name="calulate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="two_text">23 “Woe to you, teachers of the law and Pharisees, you hypocrites! You give a tenth of your spices—mint, dill and cumin. But you have neglected the more important matters of the law—justice, mercy and faithfulness. You should have practiced the latter, without neglecting the former.</string>
    <string name="tree_title">THE TITHE IS INTRODUCED AS LAW</string>
    <string name="tree_txt">Every tithe of the land, whether of the seed of the land or of the fruit of the trees, is the Lord’s; it is holy to the Lord. If a man wishes to redeem some of his tithe, he shall add a fifth to it. And every tithe of herds and flocks, every tenth animal of all that pass under the herdsman’s staff, shall be holy to the Lord. One shall not differentiate between good or bad, neither shall he make a substitute for it; and if he does substitute for it, then both it and the substitute shall be holy; it shall not be redeemed.”</string>
    <string name="one_title">Tithing in the Bible</string>
    <string name="one_txt">Is tithing mentioned in the Old Testament or is it an Old Testament practice of the law? What is the purpose of tithing? There are many questions around tithing and giving money to the church and God\'s Word has plenty to say about it! Money is mentioned over 800 times in the Bible!</string>
    <string name="two_title">Matthew 23:23</string>
    <string name="where_should_txt">Since the tithe belongs to God, trust Him to show you where to give it. You do this by first presenting your tithe in your heart to Jesus. Part of His ministry to us as our High Priest under the new covenant is to receive our tithes and present them to the Father (Hebrews 3:1, 7:8). Next, ask Him where to give your tithe. The important thing for you to do is be obedient to place the tithe where He directs. He will often direct you to place it in your local church or a ministry that is feeding you spiritually. As you present your tithe, remember that God loves a cheerful giver (2 Corinthians 9:7). Tithing is just the beginning of God’s system of giving because we can give of ourselves every day! Whether it’s being kind to another person or sharing the good news of the gospel with someone in need, God desires that we be a giving people. We encourage you to commit to the Lord that you will give of yourself as He directs. Time, talents, finances or abilities—God will use whatever you offer Him, and He rewards those who diligently seek Him (Hebrews 11:6)!</string>
    <string name="where_should_i_give_my_tithe">Where should I give my tithe?</string>
    <string name="recommend_app">Let me recommend you this app Which help you to calculate your Tithe</string>
    <string name="playstore_link">http://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
</resources>
